<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Page>
	<slogan>
		How to Become a Reseller
	</slogan>
	<block><text-block>
		<first-line>
			What can you expect from being a reseller for Intensity Glow Products?
		</first-line>
		<content>
			<xbr />
			You open a world of opportunities for your self and you can make a substantial amount of money from selling top class products. You also have the support of Intensity Glow Products and you will be able to learn a lot of things when it comes to how to use different products and what products to use depending on what you are trying to accomplish.
		</content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<content>
			<xb>All our products are tested by dermatologists and they do what they claim to do if used as directed.</xb>
		</content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<first-line>
			As a reseller
		</first-line>
		<content>
			you will also get good deals on all our products that are not available to others. Our newest deal is our 5 + 1 deal on all our products, except the supplements.
		</content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<content>
			Of course you will have to buy in volumes of at least 5 of any one item to be able to enjoy the low reseller prices that we are offering. Those prices are set so that there will be good earnings potential for you on each item.
		</content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<content>
			Once you have established your self as a solid reseller there will also be other benefits for you to enjoy.
		</content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<first-line>
			3 Steps to become an IGP Reseller
		</first-line>
		<content>
			1) Contact us and tell us about that you are interested in becoming a reseller.<xbr />
			2) Select the products that you believe that you are able to sell. <xi>We will provide you with a lot of help, information and recommendations for this step.</xi><xbr />
			3) Buy and pay your first order. Now you are on your way to make some money while having fun!
		</content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<content>
			Selling beauty products is FUN! Just to see the looks in your customers, friends and family’s faces when their complexion is getting fairer and the confidence that you will be able to give them is truly a blessing in it self and on top of that you have the potential of making as much money as you would want.
		</content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<first-line>
			We would like to welcome you to our Team!
		</first-line>
		<content>
			We would like you to make money, and loads of it, while finding inspiration and enjoyment in selling these very sellable products and we want you to have fun while you are doing it!<xhr />
		</content>
	</text-block></block>



	<!--<block><text-block>
		<first-line>

		</first-line>
		<content>

		</content>
	</text-block></block>-->
</Page>
