<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Page>
	<slogan>
		IGP Glow Tips!
	</slogan>
	<block><text-block>
		<content>
			The following is some simple but effective tips on how to get a younger and healthier body and a younger looking skin.<xhr /><xhr />
		</content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<first-line>
			<xib>Glow Tip!</xib>
		</first-line>
		<content>
			For any treatment to be successful and for your own good you should protect your skin from exposure to the sun’s harmful rays. The ultraviolet rays from the sun (even though invisible to the human eye) are very intense and they will damage your skin. Direct sunlight are causing wrinkles, dry and rough skin, and other more serious skin disorders such as skin cancer.<xhr />
		</content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<first-line>
			<xib>Glow Tip!</xib>
		</first-line>
		<content>
			If you use an umbrella use a Black colored one. The black color absorbs all the visual colors in the sunlight and subsequently don’t reflect any of them onto your skin.<xhr />
		</content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<first-line>
			<xib>Glow Tip!</xib>
		</first-line>
		<content>
			To protect yourself apply sun-blocking products to areas that will be exposed to direct sun light about 20 minutes prior to going outdoors. Then reapply every two hours, after heavy sweating and after having been in water.<xhr />
		</content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<first-line>
			<xib>Glow Tip!</xib>
		</first-line>
		<content>
			To get a younger looking and healthy skin it is also important that you try to live a healthy life. Avoid fat food, smoking, and other unhealthy habits. Regular exercise and good eating habits provides a good foundation for a healthy life and a beautiful and younger looking skin.<xhr />
		</content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<first-line>
			<xib>Glow Tip!</xib>
		</first-line>
		<content>
			Remember, beauty comes from the inside and radiates out not the other way around.<xhr />
		</content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<first-line>
			<xib>Glow Tip!</xib>
		</first-line>
		<content>
			To successfully rejuvenate and whiten your skin you have to be patient and follow the instructions on the products. Then in time, you will see the difference. All our products have been proven to work and they will work for you too. However, there are several factors that determine how long time it will take for you to get the result that you are striving for. Amongst many things, the present and natural color of your skin and your skin type has a big impact on the time it will take for you to see a result. Other factors that will have an impact on the result are if you protect yourself from sunlight by using sun-block products and strictly follow the recommendations you get for the products. As with most things in life, this is a very personal thing and the time needed for different individuals to see result will vary significantly.<xhr />
		</content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<first-line>
			<xib>Glow Tip!</xib>
		</first-line>
		<content>
			Remember that using skin whitening products is not a magical cure that will produce a result overnight, it takes time.<xhr />
		</content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<first-line>
			<xib>Glow Tip!</xib>
		</first-line>
		<content>
			Relaxations are an important and vital part of a younger and more radiant you. For example, treating yourself to a good massage reduces stress and is an enjoyable way to relax and rejuvenate your self. Getting enough sleep is another vital ingredient in getting a younger looking and beautiful skin.<xhr />
		</content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<first-line>
			<xib>Glow Tip!</xib>
		</first-line>
		<content>
			To make supplements more effective it is recommended that you supplement your diet with vitamin C as this will aid in the uptake of the supplements in your body.<xhr />
		</content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<first-line>
			<xib>Glow Tip!</xib>
		</first-line>
		<content>
			For more information contact your local IGP representative, or email us at <email data="info@igp.ph">info@igp.ph</email>. We wish you all the best with achieving your beauty goals and to truly get a <xib>Beauty that Glows</xib>.<xhr />
		</content>
	</text-block></block>

	<!--<block><text-block>
		<first-line>
		</first-line>
		<content>
		</content>
	</text-block></block>-->
</Page>