<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Page>
	<slogan>
    Intensity Glow Products – Reseller
  </slogan>
  <block><text-block>
    <content>
      IGP provides what is probably the world’s best and most generous reseller structure.
      When you first join as a team member you are automatically becoming a member in the prestigious Emerald Club.
    </content>
  </text-block></block>
  <block><text-block>
		<first-line>
      Q: What financial commitments do I need to make or how much is the demonstration kit?
    </first-line>
    <first-line>
      A: You do NOT have to make any financial commitments neither do you have to buy a demonstration kit (which is what many companies makes you do) to become a member of the Emerald Club.
    </first-line>
		<content>
			<xbr />
      At IGP we believe that our reseller members should be treated fair and not have to make any commitments to IGP. We believe that once you started to sell our products and you can see the enthusiastic response from your customers, not to mention the very good profits that you make, we believe that you will want to come back and sell more of our products. It’s fun to sell beauty products, and the rewards that our members get are probably the highest in the world and you can subsidize your own beauty product purchases.
    </content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<first-line>
      Membership structure
    </first-line>
		<content>
      Our club membership is built on 4 clubs. Emerald Club, Ruby Club, Sapphire Club, and the Diamond Club. Each club, except the Emerald Club, has a target setup to qualify you and once you fulfill that target you automatically become a member in that club. That club membership is then valid for one (1) calendar year from the date you qualified. It is automatically renewed for another calendar year if you meet the requirements for the club at the end of the calendar year.
    </content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<content>
      If you are an entrepreneurial person and you put a little effort into your sales, you can lead a team of members and actually make a very good living from your effort. If you prefer to only sell every now and then just for the fun of it then that is fully possible too. As an Emerald Club Member you don’t have any quotas to fill or any target levels to meet. You are the boss and you sell whenever it suites you. IGP is just your silent partner supplying you with top quality products and support.
    </content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<content>
      IGP’s membership structure caters for all types of members from the ones that want to sell every now and then at their own leisure without pressures, quotas, or targets to meet to the highly motivated entrepreneurial sales gurus that want to make some serious money from selling beauty products without having to make investments and take all the risks normally associated with high earning potentials. There is a club membership well suited for every reseller no matter what your preferences or ambitions are, IGP’s club membership structure caters for all.
    </content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
		<first-line>
      Q: How do I qualify for an Emerald Club membership?
    </first-line>
    <first-line>
      A: You contact IGP and tell us you want to become a member. Then for the Emerald Club members there is only one rule. You need to buy five (5) items of any one product to be able to enjoy the fantastic reseller prices IGP offers. There are no hidden extras, other fine print trickiness or any other requirements. Tips! Sell the products to your family and friends before you buy them from us and you already made a profit.
    </first-line>
	</text-block></block>




	<!--<block><text-block>
		<first-line>

		</first-line>
		<content>

		</content>
	</text-block></block>-->
</Page>
