<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Page>
	<slogan>
    General Terms &amp; Conditions of Sales
  </slogan>
	<block><text-block>
		<content>
      Intensity Glow Products and subsidiaries and / or manufacturing partners collectively referred to as IGP in this document are making IGP’s products available to the general public hereinafter referred to as Buyer according to the following terms and conditions.
    </content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
    <first-line>
      1. AGREEMENT.
    </first-line>
		<content>
      The terms and conditions as set forth herein as well as any additional terms and conditions that may appear on the Customer Order shall constitute the entire agreement between IGP and Buyer. IGP will not be bound by any terms of Buyer’s order that are inconsistent with the terms herein. Acceptance by Buyer of these terms may be made either (a) by written acceptance or (b) by receipt by Buyer of delivery of any products purchased by Buyer and failure by Buyer to return the Products within five (5) days following such delivery. The Agreement shall not be modified except in writing, signed by the parties hereto.
    </content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
    <first-line>
      2. PRICE.
    </first-line>
		<content>
      (a) The price of all Products unless otherwise specifically stated in this Agreement is F.O.B. carrier, which is the address of the shipping company IGP uses for the shipment., exclusive of insurance cost. The cost of packaging for normal domestic shipment is included in the invoiced price. Where special domestic or export packaging is specified, involving greater expense, a charge will be made to cover such extra expense.
      (b) Prices and orders are including Philippine taxes and fees but do not include foreign Federal, State or local excise, sales, use or other taxes now or hereinafter enacted, which are applicable to the Products sold hereunder or this transaction, which tax or taxes will be added by IGP to the sales price when IGP has the legal obligation to collect the same and will be invoiced to and paid by Buyer, unless Buyer provides IGP with a proper tax exemption certificate. In the event IGP is required to pay any such tax, fee or charge at the time of sale or thereafter, the Buyer shall reimburse IGP therefore.
      (c) Prices quoted are for the Products are good for a particular sale but no longer than thirty (30) days from day of quote.
      (d)  IGP reserves the right to change any advertised prices as IGP sees fit.
    </content>
	</text-block></block>
	<block><text-block>
    <first-line>
      3. PAYMENT TERMS.
    </first-line>
		<content>
      (a) Unless otherwise stated as part of this Agreement, and with exception of any special signed agreement between IGP and Buyer, all products has to be paid in full, in cleared funds as verifiable by IGP, including any additional taxes imposed on such sale that IGP is required to pay according to 2(b), and shipping costs or actions of governments or it’s institutions, before products are shipped by IGP.
    </content>
	</text-block></block>
  <block>
    <text-block>
      <first-line>
        4. TRANSPORTATION AND RISK OF LOSS.
      </first-line>
      <content>
        Unless otherwise agreed to in writing by IGP, all shipping shall be at the expense of Buyer, IGP reserving the right to ship Products freight collect and to select the means of shipping and routing. Unless otherwise advised, IGP may insure to full value of the Products or declare full value thereof to the transportation company at the time of delivery and all such freight and insurance costs shall be for Buyer’s account. Risk of loss or damage shall pass to Buyer upon delivery of the Products to the transportation company at the FOB point. Confiscation or destruction of, or damage to Products shall not release, reduce or in any way affect the liability of Buyer. Notwithstanding any defect or nonconformity, or any other matter, such risk of loss shall remain in Buyer until the Products are returned at Buyer’s expense to such place as IGP may designate in writing. Buyer, at its expense, shall fully insure Products against all loss or damage until IGP has been paid in full, or the Products have been returned, for whatever reason, to IGP.
      </content>
    </text-block>
  </block>
  <block>
    <text-block>
      <first-line>
        5. SHIPMENT.
      </first-line>
      <content>
        IGP will attempt to meet shipment schedules. However, any shipment quotation or forecast on an order acknowledgment is only an estimate of the time required to make shipment and IGP will not assume liability, consequential or otherwise, because of any delay or failure to deliver all or any part of any order for any reason, including its active or passive negligence. IGP reserves the right to allocate inventories and current production in any way it deems desirable.
      </content>
    </text-block>
  </block>
  <block>
    <text-block>
      <first-line>
        6. INSPECTION AND ACCEPTANCE.
      </first-line>
      <content>
        The Buyer shall have the right to inspect the goods upon tender of delivery. Failure of the Buyer to inspect the goods and give written notice to IGP of any alleged defect or nonconformity within seven (7) days after tender of delivery shall constitute an irrevocable acceptance by Buyer of the goods delivered to the Buyer. Use of any such goods by Buyer, its agents, employees or licensees, for any purpose after delivery thereof, shall also constitute acceptance of the goods by Buyer.
      </content>
    </text-block>
  </block>
  <block>
    <text-block>
      <first-line>
        7. RETURNS.
      </first-line>
      <content>
        The Products may not be returned to IGP without first obtaining IGP’s consent. If consent is given the Products shall be returned in clean condition and in its original packaging or well packaged. No remedies or refunds are available on used products or products deemed as not being in sellable condition at IGP’s sole discretion.
      </content>
    </text-block>
  </block>
  <block>
    <text-block>
      <first-line>
        8. TERMINATIONS.
      </first-line>
      <content>
        Buyer has the right to cancel unshipped orders at any time without penalties.
        (a) Already shipped orders must be returned immediately when shipment is received by Buyer. Buyer is responsible for the products until they are received at IGP’s office.
        (b) Arrangement for any return is the sole responsibility of the reseller and will not be refunded by IGP.
        (c) After the products are received by IGP arrangements for refund will be made at
        IGP ‘s discretion within a period of 30 days.
        (d) To be eligible for a refund of paid products the products must be returned to IGP in the same condition as they left IGP’s shipping station. Any damaged or in any other way malformed products or packaging that are deemed to be in unsellable condition by IGP will not be refunded. This includes, but is not limited to broken packages, used items, damaged products, and deformed packaging.
        (e) Under no circumstances will any shipment costs be refunded by IGP.
      </content>
    </text-block>
  </block>
  <block>
    <text-block>
      <first-line>
        9. LIMITED WARRANTY—LIMITATION OF REMEDIES.
      </first-line>
      <content>
        (a) Except as otherwise specified herein, IGP warrants the Products: to be free from defects in material and workmanship.
        (b) This warranty is the only warranty made by IGP with respect to the Products and no representative or person is authorized to bind IGP for any obligations or liabilities beyond the warranty in connection with the sale of IGP’s goods. This warranty is made to the original purchaser only at the original location and is nontransferable, and may only be modified or amended by a written instrument signed by a duly authorized officer of IGP. Goods which are replaced under this warranty are warranted only for the remaining unexpired portion of the original warranty period applicable to the specific product.
        (c) These remedies are available only if IGP is notified in writing by Buyer promptly upon discovery of the defect, and in any event within the warranty period for Product and IGP’s examination of such goods discloses to IGP’s satisfaction that such defects actually exist and the goods have not been (i) altered, substituted or in any other form modified from its original state; (ii) subject to misuse, negligence or accident or proper procedure furnished by IGP has not been followed.
        (d) All Products which Buyer considers defective shall be returned to IGP’s office as designated on the face hereof transportation costs prepaid and borne by Buyer, unless otherwise provided. The risk of loss of the goods shipped or delivered to IGP for replacement will be borne by Buyer.
        (e) If it is found that any Product has been returned without cause Buyer will be notified and the Product returned at Buyer’s expense. In addition, a charge for testing and examination may, in IGP’s sole discretion, be made on Products so returned.
        (f) THE FOREGOING WARRANTY IS EXCLUSIVE AND IN LIEU OF ALL OTHER WARRANTIES WHETHER WRITTEN, ORAL OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING ANY WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY, AND SHALL BE THE BUYER’S SOLE REMEDY AND IGP’S SOLE LIABILITY ON CONTRACT OR WARRANTY OR OTHERWISE FOR THE PRODUCT.
      </content>
    </text-block>
  </block>
  <block>
    <text-block>
      <first-line>
        10. BANKRUPTCY OR INSOLVENCY OF BUYER.
      </first-line>
      <content>
        If the financial conditions of the Buyer at any time is such as to give IGP, in its judgment, reasonable grounds for insecurity concerning Buyer’s ability to perform its obligations under this agreement. IGP may (a) by notice in writing to Buyer, cancel this agreement, without judicial intervention or declaration of default of Buyer and without prejudice to any right or remedy which may have accrued or may accrue thereafter to IGP, (b) require full or partial payment in advance and suspend any further deliveries for continuance of the work to be performed by IGP until such payment has been received or (c) make shipments paid in advance.
      </content>
    </text-block>
  </block>
  <block>
    <text-block>
      <first-line>
        11. PROPRIETARY RIGHTS.
      </first-line>
      <content>
        The sale of the Products hereunder to Buyer shall in no way be deemed to confer upon Buyer any right, interest or license in any patents or patent applications or design copyrights or Trademarks or Trade names registered or not that IGP may have covering the Products. IGP retains for itself all proprietary rights in and to all designs, engineering details, and other data and materials pertaining to any Products supplied by IGP and to all discoveries, inventions, patents and other proprietary rights arising out of the work done by IGP in connection with the Products or with any and all Products developed by IGP as a result thereof, including the sole right to manufacture any and all such Products. Buyer warrants that it will not divulge, disclose, or in any way distribute or make use of such information, and that it will not manufacture or engage to have manufactured such Products or use any Trademarks or Trade names used printed or in any other way made known that IGP uses, has registered, or intend to register or try to register knowingly or unknowingly, through any agents or subsidiaries or acquaintances any such Trademarks or Trade names that IGP has made public use of.
      </content>
    </text-block>
  </block>
  <block>
    <text-block>
      <first-line>
        12. ERRORS.
      </first-line>
      <content>
        Stenographic and clerical errors are subject to correction.
      </content>
    </text-block>
  </block>
  <block>
    <text-block>
      <first-line>
        13. APPLICABLE LAW
      </first-line>
      <content>
        This agreement will be governed by the Laws of the Philippines and applicable international laws.
      </content>
    </text-block>
  </block>
  <block>
    <text-block>
      <first-line>
        14. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.
      </first-line>
      <content>
        (a) IGP will not be liable for any loss, damages or penalty resulting from delay in delivery of the Products when such delay is due to causes beyond the reasonable control of IGP, including without limitation, supplier delay, force majeure, act of God, labor unrest, fire, explosion or earthquake. In any such event, the delivery date will be deemed extended for a period equal to the delay.
        (b) IGP’S LIABILITY UNDER, FOR BREACH OF, OR ARISING OUT OF THIS AGREEMENT AND/OR SALE WILL BE LIMITED TO REPLACEMENT OF ANY DEFECTIVE PRODUCTS OR A REFUND OF THE PURCHASE PRICE OF THE PRODUCTS, AT IGP’S SOLE OPTION, AS SET FORTH IN PARAGRAPH 9 ABOVE. IN NO EVENT WILL IGP BE LIABLE FOR COSTS OF PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTED PRODUCTS BY BUYER, NOR WILL IGP BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL OR OTHER DAMAGES INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION LOSS OF PROFIT WHETHER OR NOT IGP HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS HOWEVER CAUSED, WHETHER FOR BREACH OR REPUDIATION OF CONTRACT, BREACH OF WARRANTY, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE. THIS EXCLUSION INCLUDES ANY LIABILITY THAT MAY ARISE OUT OF THIRD PARTY CLAIMS AGAINST BUYER. THE ESSENTIAL PURPOSE OF THIS PROVISION IS TO LIMIT THE POTENTIAL LIABILITY OF IGP ARISING OUT OF THIS AGREEMENT AND/OR SALE.
      </content>
    </text-block>
  </block>
  <block>
    <text-block>
      <first-line>
        15. SUBSTITUTIONS AND MODIFICATIONS.
      </first-line>
      <content>
        IGP will have the right to make substitutions and modifications of the Products sold by IGP, provided that such substitutions or modifications will not significantly affect Product’s usability.
      </content>
    </text-block>
  </block>
  <block>
    <text-block>
      <first-line>
        16. WAIVER.
      </first-line>
      <content>
        Any concession or indulgence made by IGP or IGP’s failure to insist on performance of any of the terms and conditions hereto shall not be considered a waiver of any other term, whether the same or similar. No waiver by IGP of any default or provision hereof shall be deemed a waiver of any subsequent default or provision.
      </content>
    </text-block>
  </block>
  <block>
    <text-block>
      <first-line>
        17. INDEMNIFICATION.
      </first-line>
      <content>
        Buyer shall defend, indemnify and hold Intensity Glow Products, its subsidiaries and affiliates, their officers, directors, employees, and agents harmless from and against any claims, actions or demands, liabilities and settlements, including, without limitation, reasonable attorney and accounting fees, resulting from, or alleged to result from Buyer’s use of the Product.
      </content>
    </text-block>
  </block>
  <block>
    <text-block>
      <first-line>
        17. WEB SALES.
      </first-line>
      <content>
        IGP makes Products available for sale over the internet on our website (www.igp.ph) with payment options according to information available at the webpage “Payment Options” at the time of purchase. Payment options are subject to change at IGP’s discretion at any time.
      </content>
    </text-block>
  </block>
	<!--<block>
    <text-block>
      <first-line></first-line>
		  <content></content>
	  </text-block>
  </block>-->
</Page>